We're ready when you are ready. Okay, we were involved in the regular meeting of Miami City Council for today's day and time I didn't do this public input on schedule personal appearances anyone want to talk about a council?
I have three of these consent agenda staff are recommending items for through nine,
For the consent agenda. If there aren't no questions on any
Of those items that entertain a motion to approve as recommended?
Looks approved and second please
We'll call
What's this?
Louis
Aye
Orkett
All right
Item 10 is accepted reject least purchase agreement with our best bank
For the purchase of dinner, truck and authorized
Marocity Attorney City Clerk to purchasing agent
That's huge on this sorry documents
To consider secure
The financing as proposed
Christa
A year proved in a war
Or did we attract
Took amount long
Played together
Okay
Get it outside
Have you questions about what that does?
I do
You can't
I just
Just overview
So the day of your truck is
It's what we set up a poll with
We have
Big more
Order on it
And also having
The part that depends
Of polls
You know,
What has to do?
Rote comes down
Go around and
A poll
We currently
Have two
This will be our third one
Which they are
Keeper all this one
Just as a back-up
Other not
They had
To grow them
Three broken poles
So you can set them out on poll
And hold the poll
You go fixed
A couple of them
I've seen him
Yes sir
When we set transverse two
Patman and transformers day
He doesn't accept those
We use this
That our Christmas tree
You might have to see it
Is
This brand new truck?
Yes
Paul
Yeah, but they are
Because your transformer is getting bigger
Have year in everything
We use
Industry, we can be using more power
This is the biggest truck
You get on a single axle
Two so they gather excited about it
Go to let them transformers
Or larger industries like Hopkins
That are different places
I don't know
Stay in loan
Yeah
Okay
Thank you
So this part
16th
A quarter of $1.00
Very much
The work went into
Finance that
Art just
We need Dean
Way to bring this particular
Finance in
Out
About consent
Because it does
Our top
By that same
Those are what is our best
So I think we've been
Fair enough
You can have some of those
To do
Are there any exciting things about
What
The department
Is recommending
It's a
Three year
Turn
Payback
Cool pay back
With $9,000
And
Fifty-seven
Twenty eight
Sets
With monthly payments
Eight thousand
Three and a seven
Millions of
Million
Millions
Of course
Our best is proposing that
At three percent interest
We had
A bit also from US Bank
Different between the two
Payout
Less than five hundred dollars
So I came in both
Then
My said you shark
Your pencil
And approved
All we're asking for
Tonight is
For you to
Consider the
Reclamation of
The award
Then
Allow us
To
Some documents
That
Wait
On
So
The purchase was
Approved in a
Passed
Budget
Here's
A part
Of
Your cash flow
Budgets
Or your budget
For
Next
Correct
Yes
I would like
Appreciate
What
Christa brought up
But
Just for the record
To make it clear
My wife is employed by
Our best bank court
Not
Are individual financial institutions
but just also
For
The record
Nothing to do with
Going out
Get these solicitations
Or making this decision
And complete hands off
Of that reason
Thank you very much
Any questions or concerns?
Do we have a motion
To accept
The leaked person's degree
With our best bank
As recommended
Motion
And how second
That?
Rope, please
I
Or
Good
Louis
Item 11 is
A Mayor's
Not a nice to appoint
Bucky Barrett
For the money public library board
Julie Smith
Is serving on that
Board for years and
Years
In done
A great job
She has
Ready
And I'm here in an active member of the
Friends' Library for a long time
She's interested in filling that spot
So
Please don't mention
Not only before you
For your consideration
Second
We'll call please
Or
Louis
Item 11
Go
Open
Okay
I
L.O.B Business
Any other new business?
Stafford
For ensuring
Your packet
Presenting any questions
Any Mayor and Council
Community announcements?
Any city manager
As I said
Out of the six minutes
Stafford
I think
All we've tried to get
To that
Just wanted
Bring up a speed on
A few of
The capital projects are going
On
The
Concrete has been removed
We had reported
Needed be removed
But
They have
That done
Within about two days
The
Concret
Has Been
I could imagine
It's accepted
The Court has
Already last week
Yeah
So
Today
They were pouring around
Both the state
And
Shave structure
To
The tough coat
Is going to be
Installing about 28 days
Over
The badge of
Runway
In
We can have a runways
Part
We've been out there
You know, we're kind
Of putting those
And we did
Approach the county
As you had recommended
We were kind of embarrassed
So
That
They're very happy to help us
With that
Working with them on some
Design
Ideas
To connect
The two parts
Of having
To go out
To watch
So
I'm doing call me
After
I said
Well,
See they got
Concrete
For
I'll
I want
So
I'll
Be
Fingers crossed
That soft
Early
Center
Everything is really moving
Now
All of the place
Service has been poured
It's in place
The concrete
And it
Deschanged structure
As an
So
All
Concrete
For
The plain surface
This way
So now they just have
Math
Equipment
They're going to work on
Fancy Man
So there's a very good possibility
If the weather roads
Early
September
We should be able
And at least get it open
Do some trial run
For
Shutting down
Get Some kids wet
Yes
All right
It still got to be summertime
Summer time until September 21st
Okay
so
That will
It'll
Be opened
In this summer
Main Street
Finally Got approval from
The State Historic Preservation Office
We're going to be
Because we are having some
Financing through them
They look at the contracts and
Clarence
Of course
And ofcourse
We do have a grant
pending
But
Clear these hurdles
So
I think very,
Very soon
If
Going up
Then
We hope
To even
Do Some Public Services
Because
We know Main Street is in
Terrible condition right now
Beeper wondering
Lines have been completed
A block of water mains
I think still
Has to be put in for what
I stand from this morning
Pardon me
That may you got it now
Okay
Thank You
And then we start the storm sewer
Installation
Then Got a Block
Storm and Stoll
Yep
So that's It on Central
Finally, The Mill & Overlay has
Been Completed
In
The ADA Rams
Being installed
It was a Rim Hospital today
And saw that taking place
That's kind of good
Then
A few places
Didn't meet our standards
You probably have to be redone
I'll get it
Can you set something about
Just further south on Main
Some
Kind Of Ragging
Catched out
When we lay the blue
Once
We do
Mill & Overlay
All The Way to Steam Ons
And that would be no
Last fall laid down
Of course, Been Striping In
So
We're in the Main Street
Just so we have a number
What are The Costs
Mill & Overlay's
Okay
Can I make it decide
If you want to
Work That portion
Ok
Good
Once It's Done
To Look Great
OK
Um
That's It
Alright
Item 16
There's a German
You'll have A Motion to the German
Motion
Second
Roll Call Police
Listen
Alright